Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session one of unit six, it's
time to complete the relevant
section of the assessment booklet.
If you haven't already done so you
can download the assessment booklet by
clicking on the assessment link on the
final page of session one, and saving that
in a suitable location on your computer.
Once you've done that, you can
then open the unit six assessment
booklet, as you can see, it's Working
With Others in Cyber Security.
And you can then scroll down to page
two, pop your name at the top, and then
move on to the questions for section one.
This section is Understand
Teamworking for Cyber Security.
And there are five learning objectives
in section one on five questions to allow
you to fulfill those learning objectives.
So question one, it's asked you
to describe what is meant by team
dynamics or what is team dynamics?
This is a describe question, so try
to provide good detail in your answer.
So for question two, it's asked you
to compare the benefits of working
with others to working alone.
So what benefits does working with
others have, how can it be of benefit
to you in your working life and
learning and compared to working alone?
So what benefits are
there of working alone?
I know quite a lot of people that have
had to work alone during the pandemic
as they've been working from home,
has there been any benefits to that?
Have you noticed any benefits to that?
Then for question three, it's
asked you to describe ways in which
team members can work together to
make use of individual strengths.
So what you have to think about
here is when you have a team of
four or five people, everybody's
an individual, everybody has
different skills and different
levels of ability in certain things.
So how can that be utilised to ensure
that you're making good use of the
individual strengths of each person in
the team to make the team more effective?
For question four, it's
asked you to identify ways to
resolve conflict within a team.
So conflict is a natural
occurrence, there will always be...
very rarely you have a fully harmonious
team, there's always instances, it might
not be very regular but there are probably
always instances where there will be
some sort of conflict within a team -- it
might just be a minor thing, you know,
people not getting on or, or people
having different ideas and opinions.
So how can you resolve those
conflicts within a team?
What are the best ways to do
that to ensure that the team is
effective and everybody can work
together as an effective team?
And for question five, it's asking you
to explain how reviewing work activities
can support effective teamwork.
So when you think about it, so if
you'd be involved in a project or
you've been involved in any task
within the workplace, when that task
is done or the project finished,
what is the purpose of reviewing it?
What benefits would it have if carrying
out a review of the work that you've
done and how can it support the
effectiveness of the team moving forward?
So think about that when you're
formulating your answer for question five.
So once you've done that, if you
carry out a spell check and proofread
your work to make sure everything's
clear, you can then save your unit six
assessment on move on to session two.